

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm currently a student attending the University of California Riverside, and I'm studying computer science. I've previously attendend Moorpark College for four years and have earned Associate Degrees for Physics, and Mathematics. During my time at school, I've also taken courses in C.S covering; Software Construction, Algorithms, Data Structures, C++, Java, and Software Engineering. I spend free time researching new programming techniques and creating coding projects.

SKILLS

- C++ (oop, algorithms/data structures)
- Java

Python

- Algebra, calculus (entire series with analytical geometry), differential equations, and linear
- Matlab

• Introduction to linear algebra

- Unit testing (*using google "gtest" framework)
- Physics (electromagnetism, waves, and optics, thermodynamics, newtonian mechanics,)
- Frontend Frameworks
 (*Bootstrap/Jquery/Angular
 js)

EXPERIENCE

Part Time Tutor

September 2018 - Current

Self Employed | Riverside, CA

• I'm currently a tutor for the following subjects: math, physics, and computer science. Since I'm also a full time student, I do some of my tutoring online and in person.

Delivery Driver February 2016 - Current

Domino's Pizza | Simi Valley, CA

• Delivering food to customers Taking orders and handling money Customer Service.

Delivery Driver July 2014 - February 2016

East Coast Pizza Company | Simi Valley, CA

 Delivering food to customers Taking orders and handling money Customer Service Taking Inventory.

EDUCATION

| Bachelors of Science in Computer Science | June 2020 |
|---|-----------|
| University of California, Riverside, Riverside, CA | |
| Associate of Science in Physics Moorpark College, Moorpark, CA | May 2018 |
| Associate of Science in Mathematics Moorpark College , Moorpark, CA | May 2018 |
| Associate of Science in General Studies with an Emphasis in Physical Sciences Moorpark College, Moorpark, CA | May 2018 |

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Dean's List (Moorpark College *2014-2015)
- Online Profile -> www.DavidHuecker.com (May 2019)
- Github Username: dhuecker
- Activities and Honors:

Member of the Moorpark Computer Science Club (2015-2018)

Member of the Moorpark Math Club (2016-2018)

Member of the Moorpark Space Club (2017-2018)